Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art Friends records, circa 1961-1995 COR0008.2.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art Friends records
circa 1961-1995
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art
COR0008.2.RG
4.5 Linear Feet 3 record center cartons
The Friends of the Corcoran is a non-profit membership corporation formed in the spring of 1961 with the primary purpose of acquiring works of art to supplement the permanent collection of the Corcoran Gallery of Art. These administrative records of The Friends of the Corcoran document the development of this organization from its inception in the spring of 1961 through 1995. The records consist predominantly of correspondence, minutes, flyers, invoices, and memoranda and date from 1961 to 1995.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open to research.
When conducting research within The Corcoran Archives collections, pleased be advised of the following restrictions:
Records of the Board of Trustees (RG 1.0) and records of the Office of the Director (RG 2.0) are closed to research for 25 years from the date of creation.
Development records are closed to research (RG 3.2).
Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for the lifetime of the student, and are presumed to be open 75 years after the date of record creation (RG 9.0 Series 4).
Personnel and financial records are closed for 50 years from date of record creation (RG 4.0).
Please see the Public Services and Instruction Librarian for assistance.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Corcoran Institution Board of Trustees donated these records to The George Washington University in 2016.
Arrangement
Organized into 10 series: Establishment of the Friends, Board of Directors' records, Membership, Financial, Exhibitions, Acquisitions, Trips, Miscellaneous activities, Clippings, and Events.
Historical narrative
The first section of this history, covering events through 1981, was prepared by Corcoran Archivist Katherine M. Kovocs for publication in 1985 with the support of the National Endowment for the Humanities.
The Friends of the Corcoran is a non-profit membership corporation formed in the spring of 1961 with the primary purpose of acquiring works of art to supplement the permanent collection of the Corcoran Gallery of Art. In the fulfillment of this purpose The Friends also aim to promote the private collecting of contemporary American art, stimulate interest in the Gallery, encourage individual donations to the Gallery by its members, and, by purchasing their works, lend tangible encouragement to twentieth century American artists of merit.
In addition to art purchases, The Friends arrange educational and enjoyable events usually related to the members' interest in the collecting of art, such as special Gallery exhibitions, meetings with artists, and trips to other museum and private collections. Of their more well-known events are their Anniversary Exhibitions every fifth year.
The Friends of the Corcoran has its own Charter and By-Laws and is governed by four officers and a Board of Directors. Those who have served the office of president are:
1961-1963 Judge Edward Beard; 1963-1965 Mr. Sidney Zlotnick; 1965-1967 Mrs. Thomkins; 1967 Mr. Fleming Bomar; 1968-1969 Mr. Mark Sandground; 1969-1970 Judge Catherine Keggy; 1970-1972 Mr. Julian Singman; 1972-1975 Dr. Thomas Mathews; 1975-1978 Mrs. Bernhard Bechhoefer; 1978-1981 Mr. Marvin Gerstin
Once each year, at an annual Acquisitions Dinner, the members have the opportunity to vote upon a choice for presentation to the Gallery from among a group of works selected by the Acquisitions Committee and approved by the staff at the Corcoran. This Committee is composed of three members chosen by the general membership, three members chosen by the Board of Directors and the president.
After operating independently of the Corcoran for thirteen years, arrangements were made to bring The Friends into a closer relationship with the Gallery. In September of 1974, the Board of Trustees resolved that membership in The Friends could be obtained only by making the appropriate contribution to the Corcoran. The Gallery in turn agreed to turn over a part of this revenue to The Friends to provide them with funds necessary to fulfill their purpose. The results are an enlarged membership for The Friends, and for the Gallery, an element of programming which would bring increased benefits to its higher paying members.
In 1979, the Friends' Charter and By-Laws were rewritten into a single document in 1979.
The following section of this history was prepared in 2019 by George Washington University SCRC staff with the support of the Luce Foundation.
During the 1990s The Friends began to take a more proactive role in fundraising for the Corcoran. Traditionally, the Friends had raised funds solely through membership dues.
In 1991, The Friends began the Annual Friends Benefit, which included a silent auction and concert with proceeds going towards the President's Exhibition Fund. In 1992, the Friends amended their Bylaws to make the acquisition process of art donations more flexible, allowing for more than one donation each year.
Custodial History
The records of The Friends began transfer to the Corcoran Archives in Spring 1981 by various officers of The Friends. During processing the records were consolidated by the Archives staff.
Related Materials
Additional information concerning exhibitions sponsored by The Friends may be found in the records of the Curatorial Office (COR RG 5.0) and particularly in the collection of exhibition catalogs (COR RG 5.0 Series 6). Additional information concerning The Friends' acquisitions may be found in the Accession files in the Registrar's Office (COR 5.1 Series 1 and 2). Finally, the Directors' files (COR RG 2.0) may be another source of information on The Friends.
Scope and Contents
These administrative records of the corporation known as The Friends of the Corcoran document the development of this organization from its inception in the spring of 1961 to the present. Records consist predominantly of correspondence, minutes, flyers, invoices, and memoranda. The records are arranged into series as follows: Establishment, Board of Directors' Records, Membership, Financial, Exhibitions, Acquisitions, Trips, Miscellaneous Activities, Clippings, and Events. Within this arrangement the documents attempt to illustrate the motives behind the establishment of The Friends (most importantly the acquisition of works of American art to be presented to the Corcoran) and the methods used and success obtained in fulfilling this purpose.
These records are generally incomplete. The most significant gaps occur in the Board of Directors' Records series. Most importantly, the files of Annual and Regular Monthly Minutes are generally incomplete with a particularly notable gap in the years 1969-1975 in both files. Another deficient area in this series is that of the officers of The Friends correspondence files. This collection has the correspondence of Jesse R. Barnett, the first secretary, Judge Christopher Beard, treasurer, 1969 and 1970, Estelle Bechhoefer, president from 1975-1978, Frederick Blachley, secretary and vice president through the years 1976-1979, and Dr. Thomas A. Mathews, treasurer, vice president and president through the years 1967-1975. Of these only the correspondence of Estelle Bechhoefer is in any way substantial and in fact, is one of the more reliable sources of information for the later years of The Friends. There is very little correspondence from the years 1962-1969, hence, the events of these years are less well documented. The Exhibition, Acquisition and Miscellaneous Activities series are also very incomplete, however, the files of flyers, found in the membership series, are fairly complete and can provide details on these subjects.
Art; Artists; Museums; Washington (D.C.)
- Establishment of the Friends, 1961-1980; Series 1
  Scope and Contents
  Subject File. Correspondence, minutes and notices concerning the foundation of the Friends of the Corcoran as well as the adoption and revision of the Charter, By-Laws and Acquisition Policy. Files are arranged by subject, thereunder chronologically. These records give important insight into the basic goals of the budding organization. Additional information can be found in the Board of Directors' Records series (Jesse R. Barnett, first secretary) and in the Financial Records series (miscellaneous legal documents).
  - Establishment of the Friends, 1961; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - By-Laws, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Founding and Governing Documents: By-Laws and Charter, 1961; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Founding and Governing Documents: By-Laws, 1965; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Founding and Governing Documents: By-Laws, 1974-1976; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Founding and Governing Documents: By-Laws, 1978; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Founding and Governing Documents: By-Laws, 1980; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Founding and Governing Documents: By-Laws, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Board of Directors' records, 1961-1980; Series 2
  Subject File. Correspondence, minutes, lists and memoranda concerning the operations of the Board of Directors of the Friends of the Corcoran. Arranged by subject with correspondence further subdivided and arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent. Within each folder the documents generally fall in chronological order. Subjects discussed include: relations with the Gallery, membership recruitment, financial status, elections, acquisitions, Friends' exhibitions, Gallery openings and receptions and trips.
  - Board Member Directories/Lists, Circa 1981-1986; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors Members, Undated; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report, 1980; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Annual Report, 1981; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Annual Report, 1982; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Annual Report, 1983; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Annual Report, 1984; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Annual Report, 1984; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Annual Report, 1985; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Annual Meetings, 1979 September-1983; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Annual Business Meeting, 1983 September 19; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Annual Business Meeting, 1984 September; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Monthly Meeting Minutes, 1963 October 30-1969 November 25; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Monthly Meeting Minutes, 1975 December 2-1976 November 15; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Monthly Meeting Minutes, 1977 January 3-September 19; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Monthly Meeting Minutes, 1977 October 27-1978 August 28; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Monthly Meeting Minutes, 1978 October 9-1979 August 27; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Monthly Meeting Minutes, 1979 September 20-1980 August 25; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Monthly Meeting Minutes, 1980 October 6-1981 August 31; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Monthly Meeting Minutes, 1981 October 5-1982 August 30; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Monthly Meeting Minutes, 1982 October 4-1983 September 6; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Board Meeting, 1983 October; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Board Meeting, 1983; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Committees, 1961-1978; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Committee, 1972; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Records of Christopher Beard, 1961 March 29-1962 January 3; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Records of Christopher Beard, 1968 April 19-1969 December 31; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Records of Christopher Beard, 1970 January 8-1971 February 25; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Records of Estelle Bechhoefer, 1975-1978; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Records of Estelle Bechhoefer, 1975 July 28-1975 December 22; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Records of Estelle Bechhoefer, 1976 February 2-June 7; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Records of Estelle Bechhoefer, 1976 July 5-December 20; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Records of Estelle Bechhoefer, 1977 January 3-June 24; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Records of Estelle Bechhoefer, 1977 July 14-December 14; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Records of Estelle Bechhoefer, 1978 January 3-June 23; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Records of Estelle Bechhoefer, 1978 July 6-1979 November 21; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Records of Frederick Blachley, 1974 October 16-1978 August 4; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Records of Dr. Thomas A. Matthews, 1970 November 4-1974 December 30; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Records of Dr. Thomas A. Matthews, 1975 January 1-May 8; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - CGA Planning, 1981-1982; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Appreciation Certificate, 1982 September 20; Series 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Friends' Chron, 1976-1983; Series 2 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Membership, 1961-1990; Series 3
  Arrangement
  Files are arranged by subject, thereunder chronologically.
  Subject File. Lists, correspondence, brochures, flyers and invitations concerning membership recruitment, growth and activities of the Friends. The flyers and invitations reveal detailed documentation of the activities that the general membership is asked to participate in and noteworthy changes in the organization.
  - Annual Meetings, 1961 September 25-1968 September 16; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Annual Meetings, 1975 September 22-1978 September 18; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Annual Subscription, 1962-1971; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Annual Subscription Cards, 1968-1974; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Brochure, 1977 March; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Brochures, Circa 1981-1986; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Brochure, 1983; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1969 September 1-1976 August 30; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1961 August 8-1970 December 10; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Fellows' Thank-Yous, 1983-1984; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Fellows Card, 1984 October 10; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Flyers, 1961-1974; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Flyers, 1975-1976; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Flyers, 1977; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Member Cards, 1966-1969; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Membership Lists, 1962-1972; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Membership Lists, 1975; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Membership Lists, 1976; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Membership Lists, 1977; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Membership Lists, 1978; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Mailings, 1977-1978; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Mailings, 1979-1980; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Mailings, 1981-1982; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Mailings, 1983-1984; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Mailings, 1985-1986; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Mailings, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Mailings, 1989-1990; Series 3 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Questionaires, 1983; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Renewals, 1979; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Renewal letters, 1981; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Reports, 1982; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Upper-Level Members, 1983-1984; Series 3 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Financial, 1961-1995; Series 4
  Subject File. Reports, correspondence, memoranda, banking records, worksheets, ledger, invoices, certificate, insurance policy, banking account resolution and license for charitable solicitations concerning the financial status of the Friends. Subjects discussed include: acquisition and shipping expenditures, membership revenues, donation revenues, memorial funds and insurance.
  - Misc. Legal Information, 1960-1970; Series 4 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Tax Forms, 1994-1995; Series 4 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Shipping, 1961-1968; Series 4 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Shipping, 1971-1974; Series 4 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Worksheets, 1968-1969; Series 4 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Memorial Funds, 1968-1973; Series 4 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Solicitation License, 1962-1965; Series 4 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ledger, 1966 October-1969 May; Series 4 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1961-1978; Series 4 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1978; Series 4 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Accounts, 1978-1984; Series 4 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Shop Catalog Records, 1981-1982; Series 4 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Upgrade Records, 1982; Series 4 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Exhibitions, 1961-1976; Series 5
  Organized by exhibition and date with loan forms further subdivided and arranged alphabetically by owner's name.
  Correspondence, memoranda, flyers, questionnaires, loan forms, lists of works, insurance form and invoices concerning the organization of exhibitions sponsored by the Friends. This series concerns the fifth and fifteenth anniversary exhibitions, the 1963 William Bechhoefer exhibition, the 1962 Art by Jury exhibition and the Friends' Inaugural Exhibition of 1961. Subjects discussed include selection of theme and objects, insurance and expenses of these exhibitions. Not all files are complete.
  - 15th Anniversary Exhibition Insurance, 1976 March 19-1976 April 11; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 15th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Agreements: Abrahamson-Burling, 1976 March 19-1976 April 11; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 15th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Agreements: Cohen-Greenbaum, 1976 March 19-1976 April 11; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 15th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Agreements: Hall-Lunn, 1976 March 19-1976 April 11; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 15th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Agreements: Macy-Ross, 1976 March 19-1976 April 11; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 15th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Agreeements: Salant-Tofshy, 1976 March 19-1976 April 11; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 15th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Agreement: Von Kann-Younger, 1976 March 19-1976 April 11; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Canadian Eskimo Art Publications, 1975 April 26; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Canadian Eskimo Art Lists, Forms, 1975 April 26; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Canadian Eskimo Art Insurance, 1975 April 26; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Canadian Eskimo Art Lenders, 1975 April 26; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Publicity, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Miscellaneous, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Report on Exhibition, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Correspondence with CGA, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Notes and List, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Loan Agreements S-Y, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Loan Agreements M-P, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Loan Agreements K-L, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Loan Agreements E-H, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Loan Agreements A-D, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Lenders W-Y, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Lenders P-S, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Lenders L-O, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Lenders G-K, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Lenders E-F, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Lenders A-D, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Thank You Letters, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Not Selected, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - 10th Anniversary Exhibition Letters to Possible Members, 1971 October 23-1971 November 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Publicity, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Expenses, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Prospective Lenders W-Y, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Prospective Lenders O-S, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Prospective Lenders M-N, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Prospective Lenders K-L, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Prospective Lenders H-J, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Prospective Lenders F-G, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Prospective Lenders A-E, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Correspondence with CGA, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Reject Letters, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Thank You Letters, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Shipping, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Collection/Dispersal, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Insurance, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Sheets: Singman-Vochelson, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Sheets: Pollack-Schloss, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Sheets: Mead-Piver, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Sheets: Kreeger-Matthews, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Sheets: Harriman-Kluge, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Sheets: Futter-Greenberg, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition Lender Sheets: Austen-Field, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - 5th Anniversary Exhibition, 1966 October 8-1966 October 30; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Art by Jury, 1962 May 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - William Bechhoefer, 1963 November 11-1963 November 19; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Art by Jury, 1962 June 21; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Inaugural Exhibition, 1961 October 13-1961 November 19; Series 5 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Acquisitions, 1961-1978; Series 6